Subtitle Provide by dramacool.asia Translator [Admin.@YNG]
تم توفير الترجمة بواسطة مترجم dramacool.asia [Admin.@YNG]
=Twin Fates=
=مصيران توأمان=
=Episode 5= (Three Golden Feathers)
=الحلقة 5= (الريشات الذهبية الثلاث)
If you don't believe me
إذا كنت لا تصدقني
and insist on seeing the scar,
وأصر على رؤية الندبة،
we'll do it right here.
سوف نفعل ذلك هنا.
Is that enough?
هل هذا كافي؟
How could it be?
كيف يمكن أن يكون ذلك؟
You!
أنت!
(You want to pin the crime of treason on me in front of His Majesty?)
(هل تريد أن تلصق جريمة الخيانة بي أمام جلالته؟)
(Then I'll make you dig your own grave)
(ثم ​​سأجعلك تحفر قبرك بنفسك)
(before everyone.)
(قبل الجميع.)
Yuanying, have you found that scar?
يوانينغ، هل وجدت تلك الندبة؟
Please
لو سمحت
look carefully.
أنظر بعناية.
If I'm using her identity,
إذا كنت أستخدم هويتها،
I should go all out.
ينبغي لي أن أفعل كل شيء.
(What you see)
(ما تراه)
(is what I want you to see.)
(هذا ما أريدك أن تراه.)
(All the effort you put up on this stage.)
(كل الجهد الذي بذلته في هذه المرحلة.)
(What a shame. I still caught the attention.)
(يا له من عار. لا أزال أحظى بالانتباه.)
Your Majesty
جلالتك
and Father have no doubts,
وأبي ليس لديه أي شك،
do you?
هل أنت؟
I never had any doubt.
لم يكن لدي أي شك على الإطلاق.
Who is he?
من هو؟
Your Majesty, he's my guard.
جلالتك، إنه حارسي.
Qingci's identity
هوية كينغشي
must not be questioned anymore.
لا ينبغي التشكيك في ذلك بعد الآن.
Come.
يأتي.
Take Miss Qingci downstairs to change.
خذ الآنسة تشينغشي إلى الطابق السفلي لتغيير ملابسها.
Don't catch a cold.
لا تصاب بالبرد.
(Guard?)
(يحمي؟)
Feng.
فنغ.
What has gone into you, Chi Yu?
ما الذي حدث لك يا تشي يو؟
You tied me up last night.
لقد ربطتني الليلة الماضية.
I... I...
انا... انا...
I had no choice.
لم يكن لدي خيار.
Actually,
في الحقيقة،
I...
أنا...
Chi... Chi Yu.
تشي... تشي يو.
Chi Yu.
تشي يو.
I'm sorry, Lord Divine Beast.
أنا آسف يا رب الوحش الإلهي.
Didn't you say you were hit by the bewitching spell?
ألم تقل أنك تعرضت للتعويذة الساحرة؟
This is clearly Ji Yuanying's plot.
من الواضح أن هذه هي مؤامرة جي يوانيينغ.
If I hadn't tied you up,
لو لم اربطك
she would've accused us
لقد كانت ستتهمنا
of being in the same room when she found us.
من وجودها في نفس الغرفة عندما وجدتنا.
Besides,
بجانب،
it was raining last night.
لقد كان ممطرا الليلة الماضية.
The rain could calm you.
قد يهدئك المطر.
It's nothing. Just a flesh wound.
لا شيء. مجرد جرح بسيط.
It not only weakens Ji Yuanying's influence,
إنه لا يضعف نفوذ جي يوانيينغ فحسب،
wins the pity
يفوز بالشفقة
of Lord Yi and His Majesty,
من اللورد يي وجلالته،
but also proves my identity as Ji Qingci.
لكنها تثبت أيضًا هويتي كـ Ji Qingci.
A good deal.
صفقة جيدة.
You're scheming indeed.
أنت تخطط بالفعل.
You do everything to reach your goal.
تفعل كل شيء للوصول إلى هدفك.
Ji Yuanying is vicious.
Ji Yuanying شريرة.
I must plan every step
يجب أن أخطط لكل خطوة
to secure my footing soon
لتأمين موطئ قدمي قريبا
and gather evidence
وجمع الأدلة
to clear the Mu family's name.
لتبرئة اسم عائلة مو.
Also,
أيضًا،
I could hand myself over to you in one piece sooner.
أستطيع أن أسلم نفسي لك قطعة واحدة في وقت أقرب.
You're arrogant.
أنت متغطرس.
How will you ensure your own safety?
كيف ستضمن سلامتك الشخصية؟
Well...
حسنًا...
How long will you keep hugging me?
إلى متى ستظل تعانقني؟
I... I didn't mean it.
أنا... لم أقصد ذلك.
Stop sneezing.
توقف عن العطس.
It's not that.
ليس هذا.
I couldn't help myself.
لم أستطع مساعدة نفسي.
I just saw
لقد رأيت للتو
Ji Qingci sneaking out
جي كينغسي يتسلل للخارج
through the backyard.
من خلال الفناء الخلفي.
She went out alone?
هل خرجت لوحدها؟
Seems like my dear sister
يبدو أن أختي العزيزة
has many secrets.
لديه الكثير من الأسرار.
Today is the Ghost Festival.
اليوم هو مهرجان الأشباح.
Isn't she afraid of
أليست خائفة من
running into evil spirits outside?
الركض إلى الأرواح الشريرة في الخارج؟
If that happens,
إذا حدث ذلك،
she may never return.
ربما لن تعود أبدًا.
(Father,)
(أب،)
(Mother,)
(الأم،)
(I will clear the Mu family's name)
(سوف أقوم بتطهير اسم عائلة مو)
(using Ji Qingci's identity.)
(باستخدام هوية Ji Qingci.)
Xue.
شيويه.
Xue, you're back.
شيويه، لقد عدت.
Father.
أب.
Come here.
تعال الى هنا.
Xue, let me hold you.
شيويه، دعني أحملك.
Father, come chase me.
يا أبي، تعال واطاردني.
Careful, Xue.
كن حذرا، شيويه.
Don't fall.
لا تسقط.
Slow down.
ابطئ.
Come on.
تعال.
I can't catch up with you.
لا أستطيع اللحاق بك.
Xue, come here.
شيويه، تعالي هنا.
I made you a new pair of shoes.
لقد صنعت لك زوجًا جديدًا من الأحذية.
Try them on.
جربهم.
Come on.
تعال.
Father, Mother,
الأب، الأم،
come out.
يخرج.
I miss you.
أفتقدك.
Father, Mother,
الأب، الأم،
I'll definitely clear your name.
سأقوم بتبرئة اسمك بالتأكيد.
(The sky lanterns are bright.)
(الفوانيس السماوية مشرقة.)
(Father and Mother)
(الأب والأم)
must be watching me from above.
لا بد أنه يراقبني من الأعلى.
No one can threaten
لا أحد يستطيع التهديد
my position as heiress anymore.
لم يعد منصبي كوريثة بعد الآن.
The poisoned needle isn't from the mortal realm.
الإبرة المسمومة ليست من عالم البشر.
Once pierced,
بمجرد ثقبها،
the victim won't last more than three days.
لن تستمر الضحية أكثر من ثلاثة أيام.
Don't move,
لا تتحرك،
or the poison will spread faster.
أو أن السم سوف ينتشر بشكل أسرع.
This is bad.
هذا سيء.
There's no time.
ليس هناك وقت.
=Twin Fates= =End of Episode 5=
=مصيران توأمان= =نهاية الحلقة 5=
♪In a world of sorrows, every encounter is fleeting♪
♪في عالم من الأحزان، كل لقاء عابر♪
♪Life is short but slumber is long on Penglai Island♪
♪الحياة قصيرة ولكن النوم طويل في جزيرة بنغلاي♪
♪In dreams, mountains and flowers are as beautiful as jade♪
♪في الأحلام، الجبال والزهور جميلة مثل اليشم♪
♪All I ever wish for is an old friend's return♪
♪كل ما أتمناه هو عودة صديق قديم♪
♪Majestic as a soaring dragon, veiling the sun with drifting clouds♪
♪مهيب مثل التنين المرتفع، يحجب الشمس بالغيوم المنجرفة♪
♪Graceful as a flying swan goose, breaking through snow and peril♪
♪رشيقة مثل أوزة البجعة الطائرة، تخترق الثلوج والخطر♪
♪Twenty years forsaken, I lived the life of an outlaw♪
♪بعد عشرين عامًا من الإهمال، عشت حياة خارج عن القانون♪
♪On the Ximo River, who was left behind?♪
♪على نهر شيمو، من بقي خلفه؟♪
♪Bit by bit, reality shatters my only hope♪
♪شيئًا فشيئًا، الواقع يحطم أملي الوحيد♪
♪Layer by layer, cold blades roll up the light I once glimpsed in secret♪
♪طبقة بعد طبقة، شفرات باردة تتدحرج نحو الضوء الذي لمحته ذات مرة سرًا♪
♪Letters have long since yellowed♪
♪لقد اصفرت الحروف منذ زمن طويل♪
♪Leaving only two lonely lines♪
♪ترك خطين وحيدين فقط♪
♪Even the old yard is covered with frost♪
♪حتى الفناء القديم مغطى بالصقيع♪
♪Pair after pair, swallows draw my envious gaze♪
♪زوجًا بعد زوج، تجذب السنونو نظرتي الحسود♪
♪Scene after scene, in dreams I cannot reach♪
♪مشهد بعد مشهد، في الأحلام لا أستطيع الوصول إليه♪
♪While you rest beneath the earth♪
♪بينما تستريح تحت الأرض♪
♪My love lingers in this frosty world♪
♪حبي يبقى في هذا العالم البارد♪
♪How are you now?♪
♪كيف حالك الآن؟♪